Guide to the Lucien L. Nunn papers [ca.1863-1971]
Nunn, Lucien L. papers [ca.1863-1971]
- Series IV. Telluride Association
  - Financial & Legal Records
    - Financial Records - Cash Book, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Telluride Association - Cash Book (volume 14), 1911-1926 (Box 64)
    - Telluride Association - Cash Book (volume 15), 1926-1939 (Box 64)
    - Telluride Association - Cash Book (volume 16), 1939-1950 (Box 64)
    - Telluride Association - Journal (volume 17), 1911-1926 (Box 64)
    - Telluride Association - Journal (volume 18), 1926-1957 (Box 65)
    - Telluride Association - Ledger (volume 19), 1911-1926 (Box 65)
    - Telluride Association - Ledger (volume 20), 1926-1949 (Box 65)
    - Telluride Association Ledger, 1949-1956 (Volume 21)
    - Cornell [University] Branch check register, 1936-1946 (Volume 4)
    - Cornell [University] Branch ledger, 1946-1954 (Volume 9)
    - Cornell [University] Personals (accounts), 1956-1961 (Volume 10)
    - Cornell [University] Branch voucher register, 1928-1936 (Volume 11)
    - Indentures between L.L. & TA, 1911-1912 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Lectureships
    - Commager, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Salisbury, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Pollard, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Butler, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Sabine, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Reports
    - Dean's Report, June 22, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Manager and Treasurer's Report, May 31, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Manager, Treasurer & Auditor's Report, May 31, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Reports I, 1954-1959 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Reports II, 1954-1959 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Reports III, 1954-1959 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Miscellany
    - ADSTA Oral History Project: Interviews, Speeches, and Letters, 1979-1987 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Application Material (& Drafts) for TA & Deep Springs, 1910-1940 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Article - "Are We Moving Toward War", [1946] (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Article in Cornell Alumni News, March 13, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Articles kept by E.M. Johnson (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Cemetary Lot - Provo, Utah (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Certificate of Honorable Dismissal Requests for Herbert L. Behris & Wilbert Hack, June 22, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Directories, 1938-39, 1946, 1967-68, 1972-73 & 1975-76 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Emblem - Early Day TA (gift of Mrs. Ralph Townsend) (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - 50th Anniversary Register, June 17, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Foreign Travel - Australia (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Foreign Travel - Belgium (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Foreign Travel - England (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - History - Purpose and Plan of Educational Work (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Five Hundred Utah Place Names by Rufus Wood Leigh, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Utah & Nevada Place Names by Rufus Wood Leigh, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Utah Historical Quarterly - Lake Bonneville, April 1958 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Member Addresses, January 1, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Member Roster, November 29, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Items (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - News Clippings (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Paper - Democracy and Telluride Association (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Telluride High Altitude Cook Book, May, 1898 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Telluride Miscellaneous, c. 1890 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      Includes: Christmas poem to Alice Bird from Henry B. O'Reilly, Articles on L.L. Nunn, miscellaneous notes and financial records
    - Ledger and Notes, c. 1885 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      Ledger with records, separate notes
    - Pioneer Work of the Telluride Power Company, 1905 (Box 16, Folder 44)
      Booklet, Written by P.A. Nunn
    - Scenes around Telluride, 1906 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Paul Smith College - Correspondence & Memoranda, J.R. Withrow, June 20, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Paul Smith College - Negotiations I, 1938 - 1944 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Paul Smith College - Negotiations II, 1938 - 1944 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Personal Accounts, 1916-1917 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Purpose and Plan of the Under Graduate Work of the Telluride Association (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Photograph of TA & Deep Springs Reunion, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - TA & Deep Springs Kadachrom Slides (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Records - Men in Military Service, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Records - Summer Employment, June 30, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Reorganization (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - School's Attended by TA Men (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Student Grades, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Statement to Students - "TA and the War", Dec. 26, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Thank You Note from Mr. Reed Smoot & Family, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Books on Systems Produced by Westinghouse, 1893 (Box 17, Folder 39)
      Includes: "Electric Power Transmission Patents: Tesla Polyphase System", "Transmission of Power"
    - Keuffel & Esser polar compensating planimeter presented by Telluride Association members in Sibley, 1911-10-07; MU-2380 (Box 70)
  - Branches
    - Claremont Branch
      - Claremont Branch #1 I (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Claremont Branch #1 II (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Claremont Branch #1 III (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Claremont Branch #2 I (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Claremont Branch #2 II (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Claremont Branch #2 III (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence & Documents (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence - L.L. Nunn & Ray W. Fruit, Dec. 26, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Cornell Branch
      - Correspondence & Documents, 1911-1930 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence & Documents - the Branch Executive Committee, 1914-1917 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence - Guests vol. 1, 1916-1930 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence - Guests vol. 2, 1930-1938 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence - Guests vol. 3, 1938-1942 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence - Johnson, E.M., 1915 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence - Thornhill, E.A. (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence - White, Andrew Dickson, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Cornell University's War Memorial (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Cornellian Council Bulletin, November 1925 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Telluride Bulletin, volume 1 number 1, December 1912 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - "The Critic" - Cornell Student Publication, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Informational Brochure (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Re-opening Post WWII (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Telluride House Inventory, January 1, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - "Timpanogos" Boat (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Report Cards, 1911-1913 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Pasadena Branch
      - Pasadena Branch I (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Pasadena Branch II (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Pasadena Branch III (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Pasadena Branch IV (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Pasadena Branch V (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Pasadena Branch VI (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Pasadena Branch VII (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence re: Accreditation (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence re: Recruiting (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence & Documents re: Recruiting & Mike Yarrow (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence & Documents from folder labeled "Robert Sproull, Pasadena Branch - Pacific Oaks Correspondence, 1946-1947" (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Minutes, Feb. 1947-May 8, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Minutes, May 17, 1949-Feb. 21, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Minutes, Feb. 28, 1950-Sept. 3, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Minutes, Sept. 4, 1950-March 10, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Minutes, March 19, 1951-Aug. 12, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - TA Publications
    - Bulletin
      - Bulletin - vol. 1 no.1, December 1912 & vol. 1 no. 2, June 1913 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Bulletin - Christmas Edition 1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Newsletter, 765
      Volume 1 - Volume 22 have been digitized
      - Records, 1935-1944 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 1, no. 4 (partial) (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 1-2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 1-2 (bound hardcover) (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 3 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 3 (copy) (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 4 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 4 (copy) (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 3-4 (bound hardcover) (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 5 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 6 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 7 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 8 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol.6-8 (bound hardcover) (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 9 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 10 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 9-10 (bound hardcover) (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 11 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 12-15 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 16 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 16 (bound hardcover) (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 17-19 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 19-31 (bound hardcover) (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 32-48 (bound hardcover) (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 46 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 49-51 & 1963 Address List (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 52-55 & 1965 Address List (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 57-58 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 59-60 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Telluride Newsletter - vol. 61-63 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Brochures
      - Brochure Draft, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Brochures, 1939 & n.d. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - TA Summer Program at Deep Springs Brochure, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Summer Program Brochures, 1954, 1957 & 1959-64 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Telluride Association & Deep Springs
      - TA & DS Work Pamphlets of Coursework, Poetry & Prose, 1926-1928 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Brochure Draft & E.M. Johnson Comments, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Informational Books & Drafts (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Series V. Deep Springs
  - Correspondence & Documents
    - DS 1917-1918 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - DS 1918-1919 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - DS 1919-1920 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - DS 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - DS 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - DS 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - DS 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - DS 1924-1925 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - DS 1925-1926 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - DS 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - DS 1927-1928 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - DS 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - DS 1929-1930 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - DS 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - DS 1931-1932 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - DS 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - DS 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - DS 1934-1935 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - DS 1935-1936 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - DS 1936-1937 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - DS 1937-1938 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - DS 1938-1939 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - DS 1939-1940 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - DS 1940-1941 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - DS 1941-1942 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - DS 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - DS 1943-1944 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - DS 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - DS 1945-1946 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - DS 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - DS 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - DS 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - DS 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Balderston (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Orville Sweeting & DS, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Telluride Motor Co. - Carroll Whitman, et. al re: Audit Controversy, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Telluride Motor Co. - Carroll Whitman, et. al re: Financial Controversy, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Meeting Minutes & Financial Concerns - Telluride Motor Co., 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Trustees, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Financial Records
    - Stock Transactions, Mountain View Mining Co. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Stock Transactions, Uncle Sam Consolidated Mining Co. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Student Body Minutes
    - SBM & [Orville Sweeting] Notes (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Vol. IV, Sept. 20, 1920-May 28, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Vol. V, Sept. 17, 1921-May 27, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Vol.VI, Sept. 25, 1922-June 2, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Vol. VII, Sept. 22, 1923-Feb. 2, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Vol. VIII, Feb. 9, 1924-June 4, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Vol. IX, Sept. 15, 1924-May 30, 1925 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Miscellany
    - Adresses by P.N. Nunn, May 24, 1931 & January 4, 1933 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - California Legal Case - [Decision of School Land] (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Cottage Fund Donors, 1940-1941 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Constitution - "The Deed of Trust", 1950 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Deed of Trust, Nov. 5, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Directory - DS Student Body, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - E.M. Johnson File on Teaching I, 1934-1948 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - E.M. Johnson File on Teaching II, 1934-1948 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - 50th Aniversary, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Hollow'een, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Mackenzie Cattle Settlement, 1939-1941 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Master Plan, [1968] (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Items (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - News Clippings (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Records - Student Body Presidents, Labor Commissioners, and Student Body Representatives, 1917-1946 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Report - Submitted to Evaluating Committee of North West Association of Secondary & Higher Schools, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Student Handbook, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Trip to Death Valley, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Photographs
    - Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - DS Publications
    - Informational Brochures (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Information Packet, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1966-1971 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Newsletter, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Series VI. Photographs
  - Places: Survey Photography, Landscapes, Interiors, etc.
    - A. Electrical, Mining, and Mill Interests
      - 1 - Casper - landscape south of station - 1916 (Box 35)
      - 2 - Lake Hope - portal at Lake Hope Tunnel and areas around Lake Hope - ca. Dec. 1902, 6 envelopes (Box 35)
      - 3 - Nunn's Station - photograph of train at Nunn's Station - n.d. (Box 35)
      - 4 - Olmsted - Snow slide at Bridal Veil - ca. 1911-1912, 4 envelopes (Box 42)
      - 5 - Olmsted - reinstallation - 1908, 3 envelopes (Box 42)
      - 6 - Olmsted - second mudslide, excavation, flume construction - 1909, 4 envelopes (Box 42)
      - 7 - Bear River - Falls at Bear River - 1907 (Box 42)
      - 8 - Olmsted - overflow from flume - 1906 (Box 42)
      - 9 - Olmsted - Cottages at Olmsted - ca. 1909, 2 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 10 - Colorado Springs - Cripple Creek Mine - 1905 (Box 44)
      - 11 - Glenwood Springs - 1906 (Box 44)
      - 12 - Olmsted - Mt. Timpanagos from Olmsted - ca. 1907-1908 (Box 44)
      - 13 - Olmsted - grounds, landscapes, and scashounding areas - 1909-1910, 5 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 14 - Olmsted - high water defenses - 1909 (Box 44)
      - 15 - Olmsted - break in flume and snow slide - 1909, 3 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 16 - Olmsted - spillway - 1905 (Box 44)
      - 17 - Olmsted - powerhouse - 1905 (Box 44)
      - 18 - Olmsted - quarters building - 1905, 1910, 1937, 2 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 19 - Olmsted - top and bottom edges of snow slide - ca. 1909 (Box 41, 44)
      - 20 - Pocatello - Pocatello Powerhouse construction - 1914 (Box 41, 44)
      - 21 - Oneida - Oneida Narrows dam - ca. 1910-1911 (Box 44)
      - 22 - Olmsted - truck and garage - ca. 1911-1912 (Box 44)
      - 23 - Olmsted - Olmsted by moonlight - ca. 1911-1912 (Box 44)
      - 24 - Olmsted - aftermath of snow slide - 1912 (Box 44)
      - 25 - Olmsted - aerial view of grounds - 1912, 3 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 26 - Olmsted - snow slides at Provo/Bridal Veil - 1906-1909, 2 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 27 - Olmsted - pump station - 1908 (Box 44)
      - 28 - Niagara - Niagara Falls and Ontario Power Plant - 1908, 2 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 29 - Trout Lake - flooding of Trout Lake Dam - 1909, 16 envelopes (Box 40, 41)
      - 30 - Beaver/Bliss, Idaho - photographs of Bliss, Idaho and surrounding area, Beaver - 1913-1916, 11 envelopes (Box 40, 41)
      - 31 - Logan - landscapes, units, generator, etc. at Logan station - n.d., 7 envelopes (Box 35)
      - 32 - Telluride area - photos of Nellie Mine, Bear Creek, etc. - ca. 1885-1910, 8 envelopes (Box 33)
      - 33 - Grace area - Grace station under construction, landscapes of area, etc. - 1907-1910, 11 envelopes (Box 42)
      - 34 - Salt Lake area - Salt Lake to Ogden line, construction, etc. - ca. 1910, 4 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 35 - Salt Lake City - main street - 1911 (Box 41)
      - 36 - Ouray, Camp Bird - mine, mill, interior station - ca. 1900's-1910's, 2 envelopes (Box 36)
      - 37 - Ames - Ames construction, Telluride Power Co. - 1905-1913, 12 envelopes (Box 34)
      - 38 - Ames/Ophir - area photographs and technical equipment - ca. 1900's, 14 envelopes (Box 33, 34)
      - 39 - Telluride area - photographs of Ames/Ophir/Trout Lake area - ca. 1909-1910, 21 envelopes (Box 33, 34)
      - 40 - Nunn's Station - station interior, unit under construction, etc. - 1901-1902, 3 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 41 - Telluride area - landscapes of Camp Bird, Trout Lake, etc. - ca. 1905-1910, 7 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 42 - Beaver, Colorado - Beaver station and surrounding area - n.d., 5 envelopes (Box 36, 37)
      - 43 - Olmsted - grounds, Mt. Timpanagos, fore bay at Olmsted dam - ca. 1912, 3 envelopes (Box 37)
      - 44 - Olmsted, etc. - prints from Ted Munroe negatives, installations,etc. - ca. 1900-1910, 18 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 45 - Olmsted - unidentified group, area photographs - n.d., 2 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 46 - Olmsted area - Mt. Timpanagos, Sunset Mt. - 1908-1909, 2 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 47 - Olmsted - quarters building living room - 1907 (Box 41)
      - 48 - Olmsted - blueprints of area photos and designs - n.d., 6 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 49 - Olmsted - Olmsted grounds from pressure box - 1908 (Box 41)
      - 50 - Utah Valley, Mercur?, Olmsted - poor negatives from TB Munroe - n.d., 6 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 51 - Olmsted - snow slide - 1909 (Box 41)
      - 52 - Battle Creek - station and landscape - ca. 1905, 2 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 61 - Idaho - Pocatello Power Plant, and Bliss - n.d., 1913, 1914, 7 envelopes (Box 37)
      - 62 - Mexico - LLuvia de Oro, Chorro, etc., construction, buildings, etc. - ca. 1907, 17 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 63 - Logan Canyon, Utah - Logan Station, equipment and building interiors - ca. 1910, 2 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 64 - near Salt Lake, Utah - Jordan Canal and Jordan River - 1908 (Box 45)
      - 65 - Idaho - Grace and Malad River - landscapes and informal photos - 1912, ca. 1910, 3 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 66 - Ontario - Niagara - ice jam, plant construction, informal photographs - 1906-1914, 12 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 67 - Olmsted - aerial view of station, buildings, etc. - 1910, ca. 1909, 3 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 68 - Grace, Idaho - station interior, powerhouse, etc. - ca. 1907, 1910, 12 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 69 - Ontario - Ontario Power Plant, area photography and station interiors - 1905, 1908, 7 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 70 - Logan Canyon, Utah - grounds and interiors - 1905, ca. 1910, 3 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 71 - Ames/Ophir area - prints of negatives, annotated - 1968, 5 envelopes
      - 71 - Beaver, Colo. - burning power line and development of "Burning Pole" logo - ca. 1904, 12 envelopes (Box 40, 46, 48)
      - 72 - Ames - original Ames station glass plate of oval drawing and accompanying notes, 1890., 2 envelopes (Box 46)
        See also Box 5 Folder 1
      - 73 - Olmsted - pinheads, staff, and structures at Olmsted - 1904-1905, 5 envelopes (Box 53)
      - 74 - Bear Lake - Montpelier, Idaho - landscapes, structures, and projects at Bear Lake and Bear River - ca. 1903-1913, 8 envelopes (Box 47, 53)
      - 75 - Beaver River/Bliss Station, Idaho - cottage and station - ca. 1908 - 1913, 6 envelopes (Box 47, 53)
      - 76 - Niagara Falls - Ontario Power Company - construction - 1905, 5 envelopes (Box 53)
      - 77 - Olmsted, Ithaca/Cornell, Grace, Boise, etc. - Paul P. Ashworth's photo album - ca. 1911-1916, 1937, 1954 (Box 52)
      - 78 - Olmsted - Olmsted under construction - ca. 1903-1904 (Box 48)
      - 79 - Nunn's Station - landscapes, equipment, and people at Nunn's Station - n.d.
      - 80 - Nunn's Station - construction of penstocks - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 81 - Provo Canyon and Sunset Mountain - landscapes - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 82 - various locations - enlargements of landscapes in areas of electrical development - n.d., 5 envelopes (Box 49)
      - 83 - Niagara - mounted photos of Table Rock - ca. 1902, 2 envelopes (Box 56)
      - 84 - Madison Canyon - mounted photos - n.d., 3 envelopes (Box 56)
      - 85 - unidentified electrical site - mounted photos - 1902, 2 envelopes (Box 56)
      - 86 - Illium, Colorado - Illium flume with drafted cross section - 1907, 2 envelopes (Box 56)
      - 87 - Claremont, Virginia - local scenery - 1916-1917, 4 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 88 - Mercur, Utah - Mine & Mill - n.d., 9 envelopes (Box 47, 57)
      - 89 - Alta Lakes - landscapes - 1904, 3 envelopes (Box 40)
      - 90 - Grace - Ice cake at Grace Dam - 1910, 2 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 91 - Beaver - structures and surroundings at Beaver - 1915-1916, 2 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 92 - Grace - opening of Grace Dam - 1908, 3 envelopes (Box 47, 57)
      - 93 - unidentified sites - "L.L. Nunn Special" - sites, landscapes, equipment, 6 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 94 - Olmsted - structures, landscapes, and equipment - ca. 1905-1909, 15 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 95 - Telluride area - Grace, Nunn's Station, Olmsted, etc. - glass negatives - ca. 1900s-1910s, 1907, 10 envelopes (Box 47, 57)
      - 96 - Idaho? - book of photos - "Current Electrical Development," etc. - n.d. (Box 60)
      - 97 - unidentified electrical sites - n.d, 5 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 98 - Telluride region? - unidentified landscapes - n.d., 3 envelopes (Box 47, 49)
      - 99 - Bliss, Beaver Canyon, Claremont - annotated notebook of negatives received from Paul Jones - 1913, 1914-1916 (Box 58)
      - 100 - Beaver Creek, Bear Lake, Grace, unidentified locations - negatives and photos of equipment and sites - ca. 1908-1910, 8 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 101 - Bald Rock Canyon - view looking east - n.d. (Box 47)
      - 102 - Olmsted - view from pressure box - 1907 (Box 53)
      - 103 - Olmsted - photo of picture of Niagara Falls hanging at Olmsted - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 104 - Niagara - Ice Jam at Niagara - 1906 (Box 53)
      - 105 - Grace - Grace and Last Chance Dams - 1910 (Box 47)
      - 106 - unidentified location - damaged structures [probably after flood of Sept. 1905] (Box 47)
      - 107 - Telluride? - unidentified street scene - n.d. (Box 47)
      - 108 - Beaver - South Fork after snow storm - 1909 (Box 47)
      - 109 - Lake Hope Dam - 1906 (Box 47)
      - 110 - unidentified locations - site(s) under construction - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 111 - Narrows below Trout Lake and Middle Reservoir Dam - 1909 (Box 53)
      - 112 - Ames - view from Ames - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 113 - Lake Hope - overflow - 1906 (Box 47)